Well, oh, sorry, that was an accident.
Well, oh, sorry.
One, two, four, six, eight.
By the way, thanks for your help.
Must be tough to do this solo.
I'm not alone.
I have Remy and Sengoku, and they do their best to try to handle as much as they can.
It's nice.
Remy always opens up this window for us, so we get to enjoy the breeze.
You know, you're pretty cool.
Don't see many people working their butts off and no one's around to watch.
What?
That's cool?
Since when?
So, you, uh, good to go?
Mm-hmm.
I'll be fine.
Thanks again, Ishikawa.
Here.
And this for me?
You were taking your sweet time, and Hori felt bad because it was so hot.
So, she made a pit stop.
Ugh, you must be dying in that.
Promise me you'll take your jacket off when you leave.
These should help in the meantime.
Share them with Toru when he gets here.
So, yeah.
Enjoy.
She said they were half price.
I see.
Hori thinks of everything.
She's so nice.
She got me the one flavor I can't eat.
Stop right there!
This is what you guys stopped me for?
Oh, I don't have the stomach for two.
I'm your garbage disposal?
Yeah, kinda.
Oh, wow, your tongue's white.
Might want to get that looked at.
Oh, I bet it's the popsicle.
Yours, too?
Dude, it's like greener than the grass.
And here I am, still sweating my ass off, while you two go and have all the fun.
Whoa, your tongue is super long.
Are you part snake?
Fascinating.
I'll have to inform Remy and Sakura of this.
Could you not?
Who's Sakura again?
She's another member of the student council.
Full name's Sakura Kono.
Oh, nerdy girl.
Please don't call her that.
You know, I never realized it before, but the council has got a lot of girls.
A special hair just for you.
Hey, it's strictly business!
You really are, spoiled king, because you get the ladies and the AC in the council room.
It's not fair.
No man should have such power.
You're making me sound like a villain.
But the AC is nice.
So anytime you guys get beat by the heat, swing by.
For real?
Rock, paper, scissors!
No!
Why me?
Hori and Miyamoto have to go.
I said swing by, not bring all your friends.
Poo-long tea, orange juice, a cola.
What was the other one?
Strawberry milk.
Hey, so give me the scoop.
Are those two dating, or is Remy missing something here?
It's weird.
The two of them don't make any sense as a couple to me.
I could see Hori with the Ishikawa, though.
Wait, really?
Now would be a good time to drop that topic.
He just gave up on her, like, days ago.
She said he gave up, but I think he still likes her.
Yeah, sounds like it.
Huh.
A bit of advice if you want to date Kyo-chan?
You'd better be one hell of a masochist.
Hang on.
What kind of advice is that, man?
So Ishikawa has a crush on Hori.
Oh, crap.
Not that one.
Who was that for?
They're taking forever.
They must have stopped for something else.
Oh, I wasn't implying they were doing anything suspect.
Come on, though.
What could two high school kids possibly get up to while they're off on their own?
Uh, yeah.
I don't have a clue.
Sheesh, get it together.
Sorry.
It's your fault he's like this, Sakura.
I should have phrased it better.
No way.
My guess is Miyamoto slowed them down by dropping the change.
Thank you, you kind soul.
Since I'm the class leader today, I'll log this act for posterity.
Don't fill the class logs with useless garbage, please.
Stop messing around with my hair.
Messing around.
We finally made it back.
I know that was a really long wait.
Better late than never.
Got my soda, man?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Um, what for?
Hori screwed me.
I did my best, but I failed.
And you're the one to suffer.
Stop.
Is it enough already?
What's wrong?
I don't want to hear it.
Just get away from me.
It's nothing much.
He dropped a soda.
Damn.
It sucks to be him right now.
I can't say I blame him for getting upset, because I would be too.
Might even get payback.
Look at Remy's man being all tough and macho.
Oh, boy.
Yoshikawa?
Huh?
You always have an extra pen to spare, don't you?
Could you stab me in the arm with one, please?
No way!
Don't hurt yourself over something like this!
Give me a second to try and explain.
It wasn't planned.
Gravity just took over, you know?
Clumsy me.
Yeah, no kidding.
He was all over the place.
Ultimately, though, I'm the one who gave it to him, so what's done is done.
That's exactly right!
So get over it!
Oh, like hell, I'm getting over it!
Give it a rest, Toru.
It's just soda.
Wait.
Huh?
What?
Why is it exploding?
I tried to warn you.
I'm all sticky now.
Miyamoto accidentally dropped your drink on the way back.
Oh, so that's what he meant.
I get it now.
Here.
Thanks, Kono.
Appreciate it.
You're very welcome.
Sorry, the AC's broken.
Daytime heat doesn't bother me so much.
But if it's hot at night, I sleep naked.
Tomorrow, I should use the student council room to study.
Wait!
You sleep nude?
Well, I keep underwear on.
Is that not normal?
Oh, man.
Come to think of it, he isn't shy about undressing.
Wait, am I supposed to get embarrassed when he strips in front of me?
Well, now just thinking about it makes me feel embarrassed.
Hey, random.
But can I see your tattoos, please?
Of course.
Seriously?
All a girl has to do is ask and you'll start stripping?
You didn't even question my motives.
Come on!
Well, I questioned it when you said please, though.
Are you like an exhibitionist or what?
Hey, I only felt comfortable because you've seen them before.
What if Toru asked?
Well, sure, I'd be fine with that, too.
I showed him my tats one of the first days we talked.
What if the tables were turned and he buried it all in front of you?
Well, that really depends on the situation.
Which means...
Stop!
My turn.
Where'd this come from?
Explain.
Uh, I suddenly realize nothing seems to fluster you, so...
This was just me trying to figure out what does.
In a beat-around-the-bush sort of way.
Because, like, it seems I'm constantly acting like a spaz, whereas you always play it cool,
and I can count the number of times I've seen you blush on one hand!
And...
While I blush really easily.
Uh-huh.
Great!
He's totally creeped out by me!
Uh...
So then you were testing me to see if I'd get embarrassed.
Mm.
I'd be up to do a retest if you want!
What's the point?
It's useless if you know about it!
I mean, it is hot.
Going shirtless would feel better.
You failed the retest, too!
All right.
My bad.
But be honest.
Do you really believe I've developed the sort of personality that makes me feel no shame?
Uh...
A little bit?
Yes, I do.
So, recently, I ran into a buddy of mine from middle school.
Go on.
Miyamura?
Jindo.
Damn, man.
I'm so jealous.
You're finally growing up on me.
Uh...
Sorry, what?
As if you didn't know.
Oh, I see.
Yep, I'm a senior now.
You know...
If you weren't held back, you'd be one, too.
No!
That's not what I meant, you moron!
I was talking about your new girlfriend!
I don't have one of those, though.
Yeah, like I believe that.
It's funny to me, but Hori might not see the humor.
So her name's Hori, huh?
You and this girlfriend of yours aren't even on a first-name basis yet?
We totally are.
I got caught up in the moment.
Uh-huh.
Sorry, but there it is.
You wanted an example of me getting super flustered, right?
Doesn't get much more flustered than that.
Oh, but the next time we talk, I'll set him straight and tell him we aren't really dating.
I don't actually mind if he's not set straight.
The friend in question just texted me.
His ears must have been burning.
Let's see.
He said...
Um, you okay?
Oh, he's in a picture.
I want to see!
Come on!
All I want's a peek!
Just give me a second.
One.
That was one second.
Now hand it over.
Idiot thinking.
Mia Morda!
Are you even listening to me?
Yes, I hear you!
Whoa!
Way uncalled for!
And delete.
I've never seen this side of you.
Is everything okay?
Oh, yeah.
Everything's fine.
You know how guys can be.
No worries.
What up, what up?
Die!
He's your middle school friend.
And you say hello by saying die?
That how you always talk?
He really does flip his lid sometimes.
Hey, if you want to talk like that with Toru, you should try it.
Well, if the two of us become better friends, then maybe.
And he's shy about the weirdest stuff.
The two of you seem like good friends to me.
You really think so?
Kind of crazy how that happened, huh?
You've reclaimed the creepy crown.
There's still so much I don't know about Mia Morda.
What kind of kid was he like in middle school?
I'm curious.
Okay.
I think I got everything I needed.
Oh, crap.
Did I get sick from blasting the AC?
No.
The only people who catch cold in the summer are morons.
Hey, hey, Horty.
Huh?
Who's he?
What?
They have a new single?
Just came out last week.
She was a bro and let me borrow it.
Nice.
I might ask him for it.
The vocals are totally insane and...
Hold up.
The girl getting hit on.
Is that Horty?
Huh?
What are you...
Hey, Horty...
What the hell are you doing, Shinko?
Oh!
Hey, punch that dude with zero hesitation.
Ding-a-ling.
Stop!
I've been your friend for forever, man.
You can't even introduce me?
Second year, Koichi Shindo.
He went to the same school.
That satisfactory?
For an online search, it's satisfactory.
Miyamura, do you actually know him?
Uh, mm-mm.
You just admitted he went to your school.
Wait, second year?
Mm-hmm.
I was held back.
Which means...
He's as dumb as they come.
Stupid is as Shindo does.
Hey, I go to Yasaka, though.
So mean.
Horty-hai!
Still, given the chance, I'd change and go to Katagiri with you.
Huh?
But why?
Because you make it seem like a good time.
Or your girl's a good time.
I told you it isn't like that!
You're so cute when you're shy.
Shut your mouth!
Okay, guys.
If we're gonna talk, can we get out of this heat, please?
Sure.
Let's go chill out at a restaurant.
Or you can just leave!
That bell means we gotta switch classrooms, doesn't it?
Better hustle.
Yo, Shindo, wait up!
Oh, forgot my notebook.
Go on ahead!
Coming to class?
It starts in two minutes.
Sheesh, I mean, at least pick up your stuff.
Here you go.
Uh...
Yamamura?
That's wrong.
Huh?
What's wrong?
My name isn't Yamamura.
I was just kidding!
Everyone knows you're Yamamoto!
You're getting even colder!
Is Yamakawa warmer?
Yama's not part of it!
Kawada!
You seriously should have stopped guessing like two names ago.
I haven't talked to a classmate or raised my voice in such a long time.
Feels weird to be doing it now.
For real?
Come on, man.
Yeah, right.
Miyamura!
Huh?
Hey, that's mine.
I just want to sip this all.
You catch the Osaka set on TV?
Talk about a concert!
Yeah, I know!
It was so cool!
And how awesome were the lights and special effects!
Makes me want to go to one in person.
Shindo, you've been hanging with that Miyamura kid a lot lately.
I have.
Your point is?
My point is that I think you should stop it.
He's depressing and gloomy, and all those piercings make him look even weirder.
I've seen his type, and when they snap, everybody better duck and cover because shit gets crazy.
That's why...
Whose fault is it that he's dark and gloomy?
And I know what's really going on.
You're unhappy with him because you think he's stealing me from you.
Don't worry.
We'll hang sometime soon.
My whole middle school experience has changed.
All thanks to Shindo.
And the one who's changed my high school experience.
Because you make it seem like a good time.
Pick up the pace, huh?
It's Hori.
Hands down.
Whoa!
That's one high fever, sissy!
And mom already went to work, too!
This is bad!
Hang on.
You going somewhere?
School?
You can't go to school with a fever that high!
What I can't do is catch a cold when it's still summertime.
Only morons would do something so lame.
But you have one!
I gotta go...
Hey!
Give me my bag!
The only place you're going is back to bed, sissy!
I gotta go to school!
Don't die while I'm gone, okay?
I won't die, silly.
I promise.
I'll hold you to it!
I'll see you next time.
so fast.
Kyoko.
I'm sorry, Kyoko.
But there's an emergency at work.
I wish I could stay here and be with you.
But I have to go.
Mommy, I thought...
I can't breathe out of my nose.
Would you like a towel?
Yeah, thank you.
No problem.
Let me know when you need a dry one.
And I picked up a sports drink for you, too.
Okay.
Are you real?
Huh?
I'm real.
Sota called me saying you were on your deathbed,
so I stopped by.
Gotcha.
You fully intended to go to school,
even with a fever of...
38, uh...
Hmm?
37?
Yeah, somewhere around there.
Take any meds?
A little while ago.
Okay.
Good.
Change out of your uniform before you fall back asleep.
Honey?
Hey!
What's wrong?
Uh...
Where are you going?
I was gonna get you some water.
Okay.
Listen.
For real, though.
You need to lie down.
Where are you going?
Tell me.
Kyoko.
You've always been so good at toughing things out.
I'm sorry I take advantage of that.
Don't be.
Daddy isn't around now.
And works hard enough as it is.
Plus,
I'm not a little kid anymore.
I'll be okay.
Have a good day, Mommy.
Why?
Why are you never, ever, ever here,
even when I need you?
Where are you going?
You keep asking where I'm going.
That's what you say.
But really,
I think you mean,
please don't go, right?
Where are you going?
I'm staying right here.
Until you don't need me.
Or get sick and tired of looking at me.
Or flat out tell me to buzz off.
Or I'll stay wherever you are, Hori.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay.
Can you promise me I'll drink some water later?
That's hi.
I called your mom
and then told Ishikawa
to tell school you're sick.
Also,
I...
I'm in love with you, Hori.
Have been for a while.
Anyway,
there are plenty of drinks
and food in the fridge.
If you need anything,
call or text me.
I'll come running.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
Did he really just say that?
He practically shucked the fever
out of my system.
I'm sick and stuffed up
and he chooses now of all days
to tell me.
He knew I was awake, right?
I need to know for sure
that wasn't a hallucination.
that I don't want to make him say it again.
Maybe I'll pretend like I was asleep
and missed what he said.
That way,
we can stay as we are
for a little longer.
while you have a fertig
and a little longer.
So,
I've seen my dreams, the night is a beautiful night
I'll see you again tomorrow, and I'll see you again
I'll see you again, and I'll see you again
I'll see you again
Long袖のシャツに見覚えある道
少し寂しそうに見えた
胸が苦しくなるけど暖かい
気づいた冬の朝だ
約束するよ
近くにいるから見えないものほど
大事にするよ
言葉にできないんだけどね
寂しい
ローチ